
{
    "id": 82258262218,
    "uuid": "mI2l9+L7RA2pc4C9Oe1zzQ==",
    "start_time": "2024-09-17T16:00:20Z",
    "questions": [
        {
            "name": "Harsh Sinyal",
            "email": "harsh.sinyal@gmail.com",
            "question_details": [
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "harsh jain",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:38"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "neoz.blockchain@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:38"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many tokens would you give to the Instructor?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:38"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Harsh Jain",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "harsh.sinyal@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please select the four Learning Tokens",
                    "answer": "Attendance Token;Score for Learner Token;Score for Instructor Token;Help Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Select which Tokens are Fungible or Non-Fungible",
                    "answer": "Fungible:Score for Instructor Token;Non Fungible:Attendance Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner is a <Answer 1> Token",
                    "answer": "1:iufwkjfnewj",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner Tokens are <Answer 1> Tokens",
                    "answer": "1:djkendkjew",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:32"
                }
            ],
            "first_name": "Harsh Sinyal"
        },
        {
            "name": "Fateh",
            "question_details": [
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Fateh Latif",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "iamfateh01@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many tokens would you give to the Instructor?",
                    "answer": "9",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Fateh Latif",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "iamfateh01@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please select the four Learning Tokens",
                    "answer": "Attendance Token;Score for Learner Token;Score for Instructor Token;Help Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Select which Tokens are Fungible or Non-Fungible",
                    "answer": "Fungible:Help Token;Non Fungible:Attendance Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner is a <Answer 1> Token",
                    "answer": "1:",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner Tokens are <Answer 1> Tokens",
                    "answer": "1:Non-FUngible",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:15"
                }
            ],
            "first_name": "Fateh"
        },
        {
            "name": "Ciel",
            "email": "cmsrecuerdo@gmail.com",
            "question_details": [
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Ciel Recuerdo",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:03"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "cmsrecuerdo@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:03"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many tokens would you give to the Instructor?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:03"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Ciel Recuerdo",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "cmsrecuerdo@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please select the four Learning Tokens",
                    "answer": "Attendance Token;Score for Learner Token;Score for Instructor Token;Help Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Select which Tokens are Fungible or Non-Fungible",
                    "answer": "Fungible:Attendance Token;Non Fungible:Score for Learner Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner is a <Answer 1> Token",
                    "answer": "1:Non Fungible Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner Tokens are <Answer 1> Tokens",
                    "answer": "1:Non Fungible Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:20:53"
                }
            ],
            "first_name": "Ciel"
        },
        {
            "name": "piash tanjin",
            "email": "piash.tanjin@gmail.com",
            "question_details": [
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Piash",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:13"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "piash.tanjin@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:13"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many tokens would you give to the Instructor?",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "polling_id": "-GmrzLCLSeiyCBXZEqk3aw",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:23:13"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Name and Surname",
                    "answer": "Piash",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "E-mail",
                    "answer": "piash.tanjin@gmail.com",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please select the four Learning Tokens",
                    "answer": "Attendance Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Select which Tokens are Fungible or Non-Fungible",
                    "answer": "Fungible:Attendance Token;Non Fungible:Help Token",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner is a <Answer 1> Token",
                    "answer": "1:NFT",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Score for Learner Tokens are <Answer 1> Tokens",
                    "answer": "1:ERC20",
                    "polling_id": "SN1wX146SQij9xT864g75A",
                    "date_time": "2024-09-17 16:21:33"
                }
            ],
            "first_name": "piash tanjin"
        }
    ]
}